(Penny:)-What are you working on?
-Can't talk. In the zone.
(Penny:)-Do you know what he's doing?
-Could be anything.
(Amy:)Last time he was like this,
he figured out
(Amy:)electron transport in graphene.
(Amy:)The time before that,
he was making a list of who's allowed
in his tree fort if he ever gets ons.
(Amy:)Still can't believe
I didn't make the cut.
(Penny:)Sheldon, you want to take a break?
Your food's ready.
(Leonard:)No, what are you doing?
He's both happy and quiet.
(Leonard:)It's like seeing a unicorn
and Bigfoot at the same time.
(Howard:)Sorry we're so late.
(Howard:)Bernadette got stuck at work.
Great news! A raccoon virus
just crossed the species barrier
and now can infect humans!
(Raj:)Why is that great news?
(Bernadette:)In the pharmaceutical business,
"Mo' infections, mo' money."
Wait!
(Howard:)Maybe you want to wash
your little raccoon hands first.
(Bernadette:)Calm down.
If I had it, I'd be dead already.
(Howard:)Guys, listen up.
(Sheldon:)Can't listen, zone.
(Sheldon:)Also don't care.
(Howard:)Next week is the anniversary
of my first date with Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)Really don't care.
(Howard:)I want to do something special,
(Howard:)and I was hoping you guys
could be a part of it.
(Penny:)What horrible thing
are you trying to make up for?
(Howard:)Just putting something in the bank
for what horrible thing I do next.
(Penny:)Ah.
Lock, she's gonna be back any second,
I'm writing a song, and hoping we
could all play it for her together.
(Amy:)-I love that.
-That is so beautiful.
(Howard:)Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)When did we get
to The Cheesecake Factory?
I (THEME SONG PLAYS) I